export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is used to define a class in Java?",
    option1: "function",
    option2: "interface",
    option3: "class",
    option4: "package",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the default value of a boolean variable in Java?",
    option1: "true",
    option2: "false",
    option3: "null",
    option4: "0",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a primitive data type in Java?",
    option1: "int",
    option2: "char",
    option3: "String",
    option4: "double",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'final' keyword in Java?",
    option1: "To declare a variable that cannot be modified",
    option2: "To declare a method that cannot be overridden",
    option3: "To declare a class that cannot be subclassed",
    option4: "All of the above",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following methods can be used to start a thread in Java?",
    option1: "run()",
    option2: "start()",
    option3: "init()",
    option4: "execute()",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the size of an int variable in Java?",
    option1: "16 bits",
    option2: "32 bits",
    option3: "64 bits",
    option4: "8 bits",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is used to handle exceptions in Java?",
    option1: "try-catch",
    option2: "if-else",
    option3: "for-each",
    option4: "switch-case",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a valid declaration of a method in Java?",
    option1: "public static void methodName()",
    option2: "private void methodName()",
    option3: "static void methodName()",
    option4: "All of the above",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of the following Java code: int x = 10; System.out.println(x + 5);",
    option1: "10",
    option2: "15",
    option3: "105",
    option4: "Error",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following collections allows duplicate elements in Java?",
    option1: "HashSet",
    option2: "TreeSet",
    option3: "ArrayList",
    option4: "HashMap",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to get the length of a string in Java?",
    option1: "size()",
    option2: "length()",
    option3: "getSize()",
    option4: "lengthOf()",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is true about Java?",
    option1: "Java is platform-dependent",
    option2: "Java is platform-independent",
    option3: "Java is a procedural programming language",
    option4: "Java cannot be used for web development",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What does JVM stand for in Java?",
    option1: "Java Variable Manager",
    option2: "Java Virtual Machine",
    option3: "Java Verified Method",
    option4: "Java Variable Manipulation",
    ans: 2,
  }
];
